https://trayceehomecare.com/privacy-policy/

Why Choose Us
Why Traycee Home Care?
Why Choose Us
Why Traycee Home Care?
Effective Date: March 20, 2017
This notice describes how non-medical information about you may be used and disclosed and how you can get access to this information. Please review it carefully.
Traycee Home Care respects your privacy and works hard to safeguard the privacy of your personal data. We realize that the Internet raises questions concerning the nature, use and confidentiality of information collected about consumers. We want you to know that we apply our long-standing commitment to safeguarding privacy to our internet activities.
This privacy notice discloses the privacy practices for TrayceeHomeCare.com. This privacy notice applies solely to information collected by this website, except where stated otherwise. It will notify you of the following:
What information we collect
With whom it is shared
How it can be corrected
How it is secured
How policy changes will be communicated
How to address concerns over misuse of personal data.
Information Collection, Use, and Sharing
We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone.
We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request.
Your Access to and Control Over Information
You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at any time by contacting us via the email address or phone number provided on our website:
See what data we have about you, if any.
Change/correct any data we have about you.
Have us delete any data we have about you.
Express any concern you have about our use of your data.
Security
We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline. Only our employees who need the information to perform a specific job (e.g, billing or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers/servers on which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.
Notification of Changes
Whenever material changes are made to this privacy policy we will make note of the changes here.
Registration
In order to use this website, a user may fill out a basic form. The user is requested to provide certain information (such as name and email address). This information is used to contact you about the services on our site in which you have expressed interest.
Cookies
We use “cookies” on this site. A cookie is a piece of data stored on a site visitor’s hard drive to help us improve your access to our site and identify repeat visitors to our site. For instance, when we use a cookie to identify you, you would not have to log in a password more than once, thereby saving time while on our site. Cookies can also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance their experience on our site. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information on our site.
Links
This website may contain links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of any other site that collects personally identifiable information.
Access to Your Information
You may review or update the available personal information that we received from you by contacting our main office through our e-mail address, info@traycee.com. Please note that in order to better protect you and safeguard your information, we take steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections to your information.
If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, you should contact us immediately at Traycee Home Care via telephone at (847) 432-5190.
